

# BEN KNOLL

OVERLAND PARK KANSAS

(816) 277 - 9623

BKNOLL66@GMAIL.COM

WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ BENJKNOLL/

## SKILLS

NODE.JS REACT.JS

EXPRESS.JS MONGO DB

HTML5 MYSOL

CSS3 JAVASQRIPT | JQUERY **PROFILE** 

I am a full stack web developer, with experience in furniture design. As a maker, I have drafted blueprints and implemented manufacturing processes from start to finish, while maintaining the efficiency and versatility demanded by the project at hand. I believe this unique skill-set partnered with the combination of my creativity, detail orientation, and years of customer service will result in great success within full stack development. Through these experiences I have developed a passion to create clean and responsive user-experiences.

### EXPERIENCE

2015 - PRESENT DRVO FURNITURE OWNER | OPERATOR

• Collaborate with clients to imagine, design and create iconic, artisanal furniture.

2013 - 2015 CITY OF LEE'S SUMMIT CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

- Resolved citizen's on-demand questions.
- Created, and maintained, budget tracking spreadsheets.

2012 - 2013 NOODLES & COMPANY SHIFT MANAGER

- Trained and developed new employees.
- Balanced the safe and prepared company deposits.
- Provided fast, quality service to guests.

## **EDUCATION**

2018
UNIVERSITY OF
KANSAS
Fullstack Flex Program

2015 CENTER FOR FURNITURE CRAFTSMANSHIP Furniture

Comprehensive

#### REFERENCES

CAMERON CHAPMAN

TA at University of Kansas (816) 729 - 0339 cameron.c.chapman@gmail.com PAUL YOUMANS

Aviation Product Trainer at Garmi (816) 877 - 3685 paul.youmans@garmin.com

KYLE REITMEIER

Software Engineer at DST (913) 709 - 0582 kylereitmeier@gmail.com